（構成員Ａ）ケッ！
我々が　追い込まれただと！？
We... We're cornered?!
What overwhelming power!
（構成員Ｂ）何という強さだ！
（ビショップ）フン…　この程度ですか。
オルペウス・オーダー。
Is this the best you can do, Orpheus Order?
（ルーク）チェックだ。
Check.
もぬけの殻か。
It's totally empty?
こちらもです。　ルーク様。
すでに撤去されたようですね。
This way too, Sir Rook.
It would seem they've already moved the replica rings' production plant.
レプリカリングの製造プラントは。
ああ…。
Yes...
Be careful, Kaito.
心の声
気を付けて　カイト…。
オルペウス・オーダーは　今も君を…。
The Orpheus Order is still targeting you.
lost te saguri de sagashiteta
Lost, trying to find it blindly with my hands.
tozasareta mirai no kotae nante doko ni mo nai
But the key to the locked future is nowhere to be found.
hashiru shoudou ima kaidoku funou
Undecipherable urges surging.
found kudaketa hazu no unmei wo
I found the fate I believed broken.
mijukuna yume no naka de kikoetekitan da
I heard it in my immature dream.
saigo made I'll be there for you
I'll be there for you till the very end.
tachitomaranai kono hari dake wa
I can't stop. I hear nothing else.
boku no asu wo kizamu oto tsukisasu
How this needle carves my future.
shinjitsu kara nigetara ima
I'm running away from the truth now.
genjitsu ni mo maketara ima
I'm losing to reality now.
nani ga nokoru no (nokoru no)
What will be left?
kazoekirenai kono kizu dake ga
The countless scars on my body
boku no kinou wo zanzou toshite kataru
are the only thing telling the story of my past.
unmei ga hodokete mo ima
Even if fate falls apart now,
sonzai wo kowashite mo ima
even if existence shatters now,
boku no michi wo yuku yo
I'm walking down my own path.
It's now or never.
This is what they say: "Live your life today."
There will always be, there will always be a way.
The Minotaur's Temptation
（ノノハ）なんか学校来るの　久しぶり。
Feels like ages since I've been to school.
（カイト）まだ　時差ボケしてるぜ。
楽しかったなぁ！　南の島。
I've still got jet lag.
But going to a tropical island was so much fun!
おいしかったなぁ！　お魚。
And the fish was delicious!
連れてってくれたエレナちゃんに
感謝しないとね。
まあな。
We should thank Elena for taking us along.
I guess.
（武田・相沢）なぁにぃ～！？
あぁ？
What?!
A tropical island with Elena?!
（武田）
エレナちゃんと　南の島ですって！？
（相沢）武田さん。　エレナちゃん
今日　お休みなんすか！？
Takeda, is Elena absent today?
うむ。　水谷君から得た
確かな情報だ。
Indeed!
This is accurate intel from Mizutani!
朝　「銀河パズル警察・ポリキューブ」の撮影。
Morning: at shooting of Galactic Puzzle Police Policube.
昼　情報バラエティー出演。
Noon: appeared on a variety show with smart people.
夕方　「ポリキューブ劇場版」クランクイン。　パタン。
Evening: finished filming the Policube movie. Like that.
Incredible! You're so well-informed, Takeda!
さすが！
詳しいですね　武田さん！
エレナちゃんが休みの日は　パズルに
専念するねん。　ということで…。
Elena spends all of her free days with puzzles!
Which means...
After a long wait, I challenge you once again, Daimon Kaito!
久々に勝負してもらおうか。
大門なにがし！
あ～？
男子だけで行った　パズル強化合宿！
Huh?
Witness the fruit of our manly Puzzle Power Camp!
The manly fruit of blood and sweat! This time-
血と汗と男の結晶！　今こそ～！
Solved.
解けたぜ。
（武田・相沢）えっ！？
Huh?
（２人）んん？　なに～！？
What?!
きょう…　強化合宿が…。
きょうか　あすか。
Our power camp...
Too low power...
（バロン）アインシュタイン　エジソン　ガリレオ
ダビンチ　そして　ニュートン。
Einstein, Edison, Galileo, Da Vinci, and Newton.
It's thanks to all of you that peace has returned to the academy.
こうして　学園に平穏が戻ったのも
全て　君たちのおかげです。
I haven't done a thing.
（ソウジ）僕は　何もしていませんよ。
オルペウス・オーダーを打ち破ったのは
ファイ・ブレインの子供たちですから。
It was the children of the Phi Brain who defeated the Orpheus Order.
それに…　根本的な問題は
いまだ　解決してはいません。
Not to mention that the root of the problem is still unfixed.
Yes, the Orpheus Order hasn't dissolved.
ええ。　オルペウス・オーダーが
無くなったわけではない。
Which is exactly why I can't comprehend your recent proposal.
だからこそ　理解できないのです。
このたびの　君の申し出が…。
えっ！？　軸川先輩が
生徒会長を辞める！？
Huh?! Jikugawa wants to resign from being council president?
That's right.
ええ。
（アイリ）パズル部の部長もです！
From the Puzzle Club too!
任期満了まで　あと少しなのに…。
どうしてなんです？　副会長。
Even though his term is almost over...
Do you know what happened, Vice Prez?
分からないの。　何度聞いても
笑って　はぐらかすばかりで。
I don't. I kept asking him, but he just laughed it off every time.
Maybe his tummy hurts?
（アナ）おなか痛いのかな…。
うっ。
But would the academy be all right...
（ギャモン）
つうか　学園は　大丈夫なのかよ？
生徒会長が　いなくなってよ。
大丈夫じゃないわ。
with the president gone?
Not at all.
To keep the council working, we would need to move up the elections
生徒会の運営のためにも
選挙を前倒しして→
早急に　次の生徒会長を
選出しないと…。
and choose a new president as soon as possible.
パズル部も　新しい部長を
決めなくちゃいけません。
The Puzzle Club needs a new president as well.
どうしちまったんだ？
軸川先輩…。
What happened to you, Jikugawa?
This is a shocker! The club president's quitting!
くりびつ！ですね。
部長が辞めるなんて。
分かったぞ！　これは
軸川部長からのメッセージだ。
はっ？
I got it! This is a message from President Jikugawa.
"Takeda, I have nothing more to teach you.
「武田君　君に教えることは
もう　何も無い。→
これからは　君が　新たな歴史を
作っていくんだ。→
You must write your own history from now on.
その頭脳で！　うふっ」というなぁ。
な　なるほど。
Using your brain."
Like that!
I-I see!
I've made up my mind! I'm doing it!
決めた…　私は　やるぞ～！
じゃあ　ナ　ナ　ナオッキーさんが部長に！？
Then you'll become president, Naoki?
いや！
No!
（おタネ）お帰りなさいませ。
ソウジ坊ちゃん。
Welcome home, Young Master Souji.
I'm back, Nanny.
ただいま　おタネさん。
父さんと母さんは？
Where are Father and Mother?
The master is in Luxembourg building a new Sage Puzzle.
旦那様は　ルクセンブルクへ
「賢者のパズル」の制作に。
奥様は　ブエノスアイレスへ
風力発電パズルの調整に。
The mistress is in Buenos Aires adjusting a wind-powered puzzle.
忙しいね！　２人とも。
They're both so busy.
ソウジ坊ちゃんも　卒業後は
ＰＯＧに入って→
It is now certain that once you graduate,
you'll be offered the position of assistant manager in the POG leadership.
幹部候補生になることが
決まりましたし。
The future of the Jikugawa family's name as Givers is secured.
ギヴァーの名門　軸川家は
ますます　安泰ですね！
あとは　坊ちゃんに　意中の
お嬢様でもいらっしゃれば…。
Now if only you could find a lady to your liking...
Time will solve that.
まっ　それは　おいおいね。
Now then...
さて　と。
Let's begin.
じゃ　始めるとしようか。
Checkmate.
チェックメイト。
But there's still a long way to go.
でも　まだまだ　だね。
ルーク管理官のレベルには。
Chief Rook's level is way too high.
Your opponent sent you
a chat request.
（ミノタウロス）
「いやいや　大した腕前だよ。→
You're as skilled as ever.
Well done. Nothing less from the great Newton.
お見事…　さすが
ニュートンというべきかな」。
はぁ…。
性懲りもなく　またスカウトかい？
You're still trying to recruit me, Minotaur?
ミノタウロス　いや　オルペウス・オーダーさん。
I mean, Orpheus Order.
（ミノタウロス）「改めて　スカウトに
参上したと言った方がいいかな。→
We could also say you're listening to our recruitment again.
最後の　あの手
すばらしい攻めだった。→
Your last move was wonderful.
瞬間的な　ひらめき
解答への迷いなき飛び込み…→
Your flashes of genius lead you to the solution without mistake.
The way you solve puzzles has elements of the Givers who make puzzles
君の解き方には　パズルを構築する
ギヴァーの要素と→
それを解くソルヴァーの要素
その　どちらもが見受けられる」。
and the Solvers who release them. Both sides can appreciate it.
へぇ～！
「ふふふっ。→
君が　かつて　ソルヴァーを目指していた
という情報は正しいんだ」。
It's true that you once aimed to be a Solver.
「だからこそ　こうして　スカウトに
現れたわけなんだけどね。→
That's exactly the reason why we're trying to recruit you.
ギヴァーとソルヴァー　２人のファイ・ブレインが
そろって→
Only when the Giver and Solver Phi Brains meet can one challenge the Divine Puzzle.
初めて　神のパズルに挑戦できる。→
それが　ＰＯＧにおける
定説だったよね」。
That was POG's belief, wasn't it?
さあ…　どうだったかな。
I don't know. My memory's kind of vague.
（ミノタウロス）「ファイ・ブレインとは　そもそも
ギヴァーとソルヴァー→
The Phi Brain is the ultimate existence with both Giver and Solver qualities.
その両方の資質を持つ
究極の存在のこと。→
That is the true definition of the Phi Brain.
それが　真のファイ・ブレインの定義だ。→
That's why the Orpheus Order is looking for people who excel in both sides.
だから　オルペウス・オーダーは　その両方の
才を持つ者を求めている。→
ダウト君は　先走って
ギャモン君をスカウトしたけれど→
Doubt rushed ahead and tried recruiting Gammon,
but that was because he sensed that he is similar to them.
それは　彼に　自分たちと
同じにおいを感じたからに→
他ならない」。
ふ～ん…。
「だが…」。
えっ！？
However...
It's you. You and no one else.
「君だ。　君だったんだ。
ファイ・ブレインにふさわしい者とは…。→
You are fit to become a Phi Brain.
君こそが　このリングをつけるに
ふさわしい」。
You are fit to bear this ring.
A replica ring? It's a fake.
レプリカリング…　偽物じゃないか。
「リングが　偽物かどうかなんて
どうでもいいんだ。→
Does it matter if it's an original or a fake?
大事なのは　君が　本物の
ファイ・ブレインになれるかどうかだ。→
What matters is whether you can become a true Phi Brain or not.
違うかい？」。
Am I wrong?
Thanks for the invitation, but I've given up already.
せっかくのお誘いは
ありがたいけど→
僕は　もう諦めたんだ。
「本当に　そうかな？」。
I wonder about that.
（おタネ）坊ちゃん　夜更かしは
お体に障りますよ。
Young Master, it's bad for your health to stay up late!
Oh, yeah.
「ふふふっ　また連絡するよ」。
I'll be calling again.
（おタネ）お友達とお電話ですか？
Are you on the phone with a friend?
いや…　独り言。
No, just talking to myself.
（タマキ）はぁ…。
おはようございます。　副会長！
Good morning, Vice President!
ああ　井藤さん…　大門君。
おはようっす。
Hello, Itou... and Daimon.
Hey.
わっ！　どうしたんですか！？
その目の下のクマ！？
What's with those rings under your eyes?
ゆうべ　全然眠れなくって。
う　うっ…。
I couldn't sleep at all last night.
私ね…。
うっ？
You know, I...
I've been thinking the president would always be the president.
私　会長は　ずっと会長だと
思ってた。
任期満了まで　一緒に
生徒会で働けたら→
I had hoped we could work together until our terms were over.
寂しいけど　納得できたと思う…。
It would have been sad, but I could've accepted it.
On the other hand, this is too sudden...
でも　あまりにも
突然だったから…。
What are you murmuring about?
何　こそこそ話してんだよ。
男子は黙ってなさい！
Boys should shut up!
副会長は　生徒会長になんねえの？
（タマキ・ノノハ）えっ！？
Won't you be the new president?
軸川先輩の後っつったら　千枝乃
先輩しか　いねえと思うんだけど。
I'd say you're the only one who could follow in Jikugawa's footsteps.
私が！？　無理よ。
軸川会長の後を継ぐなんて。
Me? No way... I could never follow him.
≪（相沢）ご登校中の皆様～！→
Everyone heading to class, listen up!
The next student council president should be Takeda Naoki!
次期生徒会　会長には　武田ナオキを
よろしくお願いしま～す。
They've already started campaigning?
もう　選挙活動してる！
なぜに　あの人が！？
Why him?!
バカは行動だけは早えからな。
Idiots know how to act quickly...
The president told me this:
（武田）
生徒会長は　私に　こう言いました。
「武田君ならば　きっと　僕以上に→
"Takeda, I'm sure that you can raise more geniuses in this school than I ever could."
この学園に　天才風を
吹かせてくれるだろう」と～！
Yes! I was accepted and recommended to become the next president by Jikugawa!
そう！　私こそが　生徒会長に
認められ　あとを託された後継者！
いや！
二代目軸川ソウジというべき天才！
Me, the genius who could be called the second Jikugawa Souji!
Takeda Naoki for the next student council president!
どうか　次期生徒会会長には
武田ナオキ！
次期パズル部部長　内定済みの
武田ナオキに　清き１票を！
Vote for me, the top candidate for the Puzzle Club's presidency!
The... The second Jikugawa Souji?!
に　二代目　軸川ソウジですって～！
Vice Prez?
副会長？
あっ。
President Jikugawa's council...
軸川会長の生徒会…
有象無象に　私利私欲で→
I won't allow the mob to ruin it for their own puny desires and ambitions!
メチャクチャにされて
たまるもんですか！
Huh?
えっ！？
決めたわ。
私も生徒会長に立候補します！
I've decided! I'll be running for student council president as well!
健全なパズルは
健全な学園生活に宿る。
Healthy puzzles are only born in a healthy school environment.
私は　軸川体制を引き継ぎ→
I will walk in the footsteps of Jikugawa Souji
解放された知性と　秩序ある
学園生活の両立を目指します。
and support free knowledge and an orderly high school life.
Please vote!
お願いしま～す！
（奥寺）次期生徒会長には　奥寺八郎
奥寺八郎をよろしくお願いします。
The next president should be Okudera Hachirou!
Okudera Hachirou and none other!
√学園で　放送委員　図書委員を
歴任し→
I have been in charge of the school radio and the academy's library,
and I also come from the puzzle world's elite
パズルＷ杯　アジア予選　第８位という
輝かしい成績を残した→
as my genius older brother won eighth place
in the Asian preliminaries of the Puzzle World Cup!
天才パズラーを兄に持つ
パズル界のサラブレット。
この奥寺八郎を　皆様の…
皆様の清き１票を→
I am Okudera Hachirou!
Please vote for me: Okudera Hachirou!
この奥寺八郎に　お願いします！
Everyone who votes for me will get a special presidential honor!
私に投票してくれた方には　今なら
生徒会長公認の称号を贈呈！
Clubs that vote for me as a group will enjoy advantages as well!
組織票を入れてくれた部活には→
いろいろ便宜を図って
差し上げよう！
部費関係のことで！
Especially in regards to financing!
（男子生徒１）頑張ってください。
（タマキ）ありがとうございます。
I wish you all the best!
Thank you very much.
（男子生徒２）頑張ってね。
Keep up the good work!
Thank you, I will!
ありがとうございます。
頑張ります。
The school is in chaos.
大混乱じゃねえか。
軸川先輩のせいでよ。
This is all Jikugawa's fault.
（キュービック）軸川先輩にも
何か理由があるんだよ。
Jikugawa must have his reasons.
だったら　俺たちに話してくれても
いいじゃねえか。　仲間だろ？
Then he should tell us about it! We're friends!
Well...
それは…。
（アナ）ぽわわん　かち～ん。
アナ？
Love-puff, cha-ching!
Ana?
明るいんだけど　冷たい感じ…
ソウジが　よく見えない…。
It's bright but cold.
I can't really see Souji.
うん…　軸川先輩は　きっと
ぽわわん　かち～んなんだ。
Yeah. Jikugawa is love-puff cha-ching like that.
I see...
なるほどな…　って　分かるかよ！
Wait, no I don't!
Vote for Takeda Naoki!
≪（拡声機）（武田）この武田ナオキに！
≪（奥寺）奥寺八郎に　清き１票を！
Vote for Okudera Hachirou!
Boy, they sure are fired up!
やれやれ　大騒ぎだね！
It's all your fault.
あんたのせいだろ。
カイト君。
Kaito?
何で　いきなり
辞めちまったんだよ　先輩。
Why did you quit so suddenly?
ふっ…　旅にでも　出ようかな…
なんて思っただけさ。
はぁ？
I should go on a trip... Well, I thought about that.
Huh?
カイト君は　オルペウスの腕輪を拒否した。
ファイ・ブレインになることも。
You've rejected the Orpheus Armlet
and the act of becoming a Phi Brain.
セクションΦは　開店休業状態。
The Section Phi is as good as dead.
僕の役目も
終わったようなものだからね。
My job is over as well.
らしくねえじゃん。
おせっかいな　あんたにしちゃ。
That's not like you. You're always such a busybody.
君は　僕の何を知ってるんだい？
えっ！？
What do you know about me?
Huh?
そもそも生徒会長なんて
キャラじゃなかったんだ。
I wasn't fit for being the council president at all.
僕　本当は　自分勝手な
わがままな人間なんだよ。
I'm a selfish, inconsiderate person.
But now this weight is off my shoulders.
でも　これで肩の荷が下りた。
君たちがいれば
学園は大丈夫だし→
The school will be all right as long as you guys are around,
生徒会も　千枝乃君が
何とかしてくれるさ。
and Chieno will do something about the council.
I'm a bit worried about the Puzzle Club though.
パズル部は…
ちょっと心配だけどね。
マジで言ってんのかよ。
もちろん。
Are you serious?
Of course.
まっ　いっか。　あんたの　こった。
Well, whatever. It's your business.
考えてることとか
やりてえこととか　あんだろうし。
I guess you've got stuff on your mind and stuff you wanna do.
Huh?
えっ！？
旅に出んだろ？
お土産　待ってっからな。
You're going on a trip?
Bring us some souvenirs then.
カイト君…。
Kaito...
招待状…。　やれやれ…　これの
アドレスまで知っているとはね。
An invitation? They even managed to find this address...
この場所は！？
That place!
あ～っ　チラシが足りない！　う～っ。
We don't have enough flyers!
他のコピー機は？
Where's another copier?
あれ！？　軸川先輩？
Huh? Jikugawa?
どこ行くんだろう？　軸川先輩。
Where is he going?
Is that Tamaki?
それ　タマキ？
そう。
Yeah!
She doesn't look human.
人間には見えねえぜ。
ノノハ？
Nonoha?
軸川先輩が！？
（ギャモン・キュービック）あっ！？
Jikugawa's what?!
「腕輪の間にて待つ…」　か。
Waiting in the Chamber of the Armlet, huh?
I never thought I'd come back here again.
まさか　また　ここに
来ることになるとはね。
軸川先輩が裏山に？
Jikugawa went up the mountain?
ああ。　ノノハが追っかけたんだけど
見失ったってよ。
Yeah.
Nonoha was on his trail, but she lost sight of him.
えっ…。
なんか思い詰めたような
顔してたらしいぜ。
She said he had this determined look on his face.
ああっ。　まさか…　うっ。
Don't tell me...
裏山？
（ギャモン・カイト）あっ。
The mountain?
あそこには…。
Up there...
心の声
滑車のパズルと　ミノタウロス…
それに…。
There's the puzzle of cogs, the Minotaur, and...
オルペウスの腕輪。
the Orpheus Armlet.
（キュービック）見つけた！　これを見て。
Found him!
Look at this!
あぁ。
軸川先輩が…　どうして　そこに！？
Jikugawa... Why is he there?
Welcome, Newton.
（ミノタウロス）「ようこそ　ニュートン」。
This...
これは…。
Yes, it's a puzzle you know.
「そう。　君も　よく知っている
パズルだ。→
だが　以前のものとは
少しだけ　ルールが違う。→
But the rules are a bit different from before.
If you pull the wrong rope, the bombs will explode, and the cave will collapse.
不正解の綱を引きば　爆弾が爆発し
地下空間は崩落…。→
The whole Root Academy would sink into the hole.
地上の　√学園は　奈落の底に
沈むこととなるだろう」。
I see. That's terrible.
なるほど…　それは大変だ。
だけど　困ったね。
But there's a problem.
僕はギヴァーで　パズルを解くのは
得意じゃないんだけど。
I'm a Giver; solving puzzles isn't my specialty.
In that case...
（ミノタウロス）「だったら…
それを使うといいよ」。
Use that.
Hey, is that...
おいおい　こいつは…！
レプリカリング！
A replica ring!
どうなってんだよ　こりゃ！
うっ…。
What going on?!
ん。
話して…　キューちゃん。
Speak up, Cubie.
うっ。
おい　お前　なんか知ってんのか？
You know something?!
Tell us already!
さっさと話しちまえ！
Jikugawa told me to keep it secret.
軸川先輩から　黙ってるように
言われたんだ。
オルペウス・オーダーが　コンタクトを！？
回想
ああ。
The Orpheus Order contacted you?!
Yeah.
レプリカリングの次の実験台に
回想
どうやら　僕が選ばれたらしい。
They've chosen me to be the next lab rat for their replica rings.
あっ！？
回想
でも　これは　チャンスだ。
But this is our chance.
うまくいけば　リングの情報を
回想
手に入れられるかもしれない。
If we do this right, we may be able to gather data on the rings.
The rings' weaknesses and how to take them off.
回想
リングの弱点　外し方…。
If we can learn that, then wearing it is a small price.
回想
それが分かるなら
僕がリングをつけたって…。
回想
あっ。
それが…　今の僕に
できる　たった１つの事だからね。
Although...
That's the only thing I can do.
回想　危険だよ　そんなの。
あんな
偽物に　飲み込まれる僕じゃない。
It's too dangerous!
A mere fake wouldn't be able to overwhelm me.
回想
逆に　僕が　コントロールしてみせるさ。
I'll control it instead!
回想
軸川先輩…。
Jikugawa...
Of course, we can't know what may or may not happen.
回想
もちろん　ものが　ものだけに
何が起きるか分からない。
回想
最悪の場合に備えて　身辺整理と
覚悟だけは　しておかないとね。
I should get my affairs straight for the worst case scenario.
じゃあ　先輩が
生徒会長を辞めたってのは…。
So that's why he quit the council?
うん…。
うっ。　あの　お人よしが！
He's just too nice!
Kaito!
カイト！
（ミノタウロス）「どうしたのかな？
早く解かないと　学園が危ないよ」。
What's wrong?
The school will be in danger if you don't solve it in time.
「恐れずに　リングをつけてごらん。→
Ignore your fears, and put on the ring.
そうすれば　君は　ファイ・ブレインとなり
学園を救うことができる」。
Then you will become a Phi Brain and save the school.
ずいぶんと　安っぽい
心の声
あおり文句だね。
Such a clichéd recruitment line...
心の声
ファイ・ブレインか…。
Phi Brain, huh?
心の声
僕を拒絶したあの腕輪と
カイト君が契約したとき→
The moment the ring that rejected me accepted Kaito, I decided.
心の声
僕の心は決まったんだ。
I entrusted my dream to him and let no one get in his way.
心の声
彼に…　僕の夢を託そうって。
その邪魔はさせない…。
危ねえこと　１人で
心の声
抱え込みやがって！
You shouldn't take on such dangerous burdens alone!
心の声
何が　僕のキャラじゃねえだよ！
"I'm not fit at all," my ass!
You're the best fit for being the student council president!
心の声
あんた　やっぱり
生徒会長じゃねえか　軸川ソウジ！
Boy, oh, boy. I have to choose now.
やれやれ…　これは　お手上げだね。
学園と一緒に死ぬか…　このリングを
つけるか…　２つに１つ…。
Either I die with the academy or I put on the ring.
Those are my choices.
その時が来たようだね。
心の声
The time has come.
あっ…　カイト！
Kaito!
軸川先輩は？
≪ここだよ。
Where's Jikugawa?
I'm here!
軸川先輩…。
学園は　もう大丈夫だよ…。
Jikugawa?
The school is safe.
（キュービック）レプリカリングは？
ああ　問題ない。
And the replica ring?
Don't worry about that either.
だから…　僕と戦ってくれ　カイト君。
So... let's fight, Kaito.
（ホイスト）
レプリカリング・ベータ
軸川ソウジに実装されました。
Jikugawa Souji has put on the beta replica ring.
eiyuu kidori itsu datte shinjita muteki no kankaku
I think I'm a hero and believe that I'm invincible.
tatakatte iru no wa chikyuu no tame nanka janai
I'm not fighting for the world.
motto mai peesu de
It's for a more personal,
sou motto shoujikina negai no tame
a more honest wish.
nando to naku kizutsuite mo
No matter how many times I'm hurt